Number nine, they have a right to remain claim for Pensacola, GRDA,
relaxing scene and associated complaint proceedings in the amount of $5,032.50.
So you should have in your packets some background on this, which is for services and
disbursements incurred from July 7th to July 27th to 2022.
On behalf of the City of Miami, on FERC's new proceeding to investigate
GDRDA's Transhibition rates and updating the City team on when FERC may issue a decision regarding the complaint
remand.
Second.
Stand.
Ten.
Thank you, Mr. Bush and we approve.
And we're delighted.
We're in a little of the following end of contracts
from fiscal year 2223.
Boose and Boose Electric, HK Electric, Livingston Ponding,
County Elevator, and Peter's Paving.
Crystal.
So these are service contracts annual on tracks.
They actually started a year or maybe two years ago
for some of them.
This is just extending that our annual contracts
have built-in opportunities to renew,
making them about four-year contracts.
But both parties have to agree to extend the term.
So this year, because of the,
of the, all of that happened with COVID and the market
and fluctuation, this year we include, or this last round,
we included an opportunity for the contractors
to include a two percent increase in their bid.
They're hourly rates.
Only one of the contractors did that.
And I believe it was, you can see that they're in your packet.
I think it was Livingston Ponding, possibly HK, one of those two.
I haven't heard any reason to not renew these contracts
from our department heads.
So just ask that you agree to renew on the same terms.
These are contractors to do work for the city.
I hope we have a lot to get you.
On call, yes, for our facilities.
I want to move on to the brief.
Thank you.
Hi.
Well, waveform a bit of procedures.
Part of the purchasing policy for emergency,
replacement of the pump motor and wiring for well number eight,
which is not replaced in a timely manner.
Good jeopardized public health safety.
I'm going to approve the purchase for California.
So this is for Willay, out on 22nd, and I'm
streets of Yolong, and I'm going to approve the River
Jacks to the right.
There's a water tower right there.
So certainly that Will is out.
And our person policy does not allow us to purchase it
with quotes because it's the policy allows.
So we talked about the ban.
This allows us to get the procedure going.
And I think other can explain more about why we need to.
But we will follow up with an ordinance probably
at the next meeting to make sure all of our eyes
are dotted and deez are crossed.
But it does exceed what our current manual purchasing
manual allows, which is yet another reason why we need to update
our manual, which is in the starting processes of doing that.
So this is considered an emergency situation.
And that's why the manual does allow the council
overwrite the manual when needed.
And the situation that we're in is we're OK.
But by losing this pump, we're putting
undue stress on another pump that's having to make up the difference.
And that pump is working over time and providing water as needed.
But it also, because of the pressure that it's having to put,
it's putting pressure on our infrastructure unnecessarily.
And we don't want to do that anything like the time,
because we could cause links.
That's what we produce is a thousand.
This is the only thing he can't talk to you about the details.
I mean, it's in June, I don't believe 70 million.
Does that mean go on for a while, but issues with that pump?
Since July 17th.
It started.
There was so a pump being that it would have been used.
Yeah, I know there's certainly been some work on the past.
So you actually got some quotes.
Yeah, there's three quotes in there.
So there's a quote from Crafters.
There's a quote from Mr. Pomp and there's quote from JCI.
So Crafters is a lowest.
That's what you're gonna go with.
He's done a lot of work around talent, and we're saying they have a lot of, you know, they're happy to take it to anybody out there, John Dan, show you a funny story Kevin told me about it, one of the former citizens in the year.
We thought that they could change on the very bottom.
Peter of I and Paul.
And we thought they were seeing, like we thought about that.
How old is that pump that's there?
It was rebuilt in 2005.
So it was rebuilt.
They worked I have before that.
It's probably currently that pump is actually, the pump itself is in two pieces that actually broke in half and pulled it out.
And then the motor, all of the oil from inside the motor, came out as they pulled it out of the hole.
We did get a lot of use of that.
So if we have a fire out in that area, are we going to be in trouble?
Now we are right.
But then we were pushing a lot of water, and the river's not going to call us.
I mean, we're at the...
So if we say yes, I'm curious this, what's the difference between what your normal process is in this.
So I'm crazy going to talk about this in the 21 days.
We have to go.
So basically the only difference is time.
So yeah, instead of putting it out to bed, we're actually using these three quotes and asking the council to let us move forward with this lowest bid that we had a quote.
There's a lot to expect to see at the pump 15 years.
So that's about 15 to 20 years.
So they all...
Oh yeah, I think this is the first of them.
So held as the pump that we're relying on to make up the difference while this one's down.
Currently we're pumping water out of the hop center, which is fed by, so we're actually
relying on those five to make up the difference that this one will normally care.
Nope.
I don't want those calls here.
I don't care.
Bo gets a bottle.
So the ordinance that we're looking at is that I'm going to put emergency clauses in place that will allow us to make choices and decisions like that.
So that's one of the things we'd like to bring to the council.
Yeah.
We'd like to make sure we've got good options built into the menu that you all are comfortable with.
But that's a longer term project.
So the immediate will be to allow this.
Get everything straight enough.
So this is legal.
We're violating.
So like we are we are in excess in doing this.
We are in excess of what the state law allows.
But the state law allows us to deviate from what it says.
If we do it by ordinance.
And so that's why we're going to have an ordinance for this specific thing.
But in the longer range picture, we need to revamp the whole purchasing manual.
Today we're asking you for approval to move forward.
So that would we bring you an ordinance at the next meeting.
You'll approve.
So where's the money coming from?
Yeah.
That other thing is.
Think emotion that wakes up the second.
All right.
Thank you.
13.
The warbed C22 dash 46 for annual.
As needed.
It all caught open transition warning labor for water line replacement.
To be town construction.
Call.
construction going to enterprises, Cooper Resources, Broadhead Boring, Haskell, Fabrication and Construction.
A period contract contingent upon the submission, a required contract document and a
period city manager, or his designated sign to proceed.
So this is where I know what are my contact replacement for Boring and for open transfers,
with where they date they are at the water line end.
Obviously, we are doing lots of road work.
So we are trying to get out in front of all the road work because we don't want to replace
a brand new road and have a bad water line or, you know,
to rely on issues so we are doing lots of water work out there.
So we are just going to go on for a few years.
So currently we have at least three of those contacture right now,
doing some projects, you know, kind of finishing up some jobs from that last thing.
You know, we are about to finish up the street.
Are you sure you are out over here?
Yeah.
So the thing people don't understand too is I brought it all and then dealing,
excuse me, talking to that, I don't, the two leads for the water performance.
Sorry, to kind of talk about it, but it takes a long time.
So you put the water main in and then you have to flush it and then you have to send it all
for samples because you don't want to connect the services on to the water main that's not,
you know, had the back teeth and everything taken.
So it takes time.
I mean, I don't know if you would like the time it takes, but
else it don't want to give somebody water that has bacteria in it.
And then once that line clears, approval, then we can start to do the service line on to it.
So that's why you use the line put in, all the holes still that stuck back out.
As the question is, you mean, like, I keep calling it dealing.
It's all in dealing there on the crew together, so that's why I mean, he's calling it D&D.
So they can answer any questions on it.
And we do have a lot of projects going on. It's pretty neat.
I mean, all the water line stuff we got is going on.
And also when they're doing the work on D Street, they've got to pull off and go fix the water leak or other stuff too, right?
Because you guys don't have pretty small crew.
No, we're talking about D Street over here.
Northwest.
Just right behind us.
It's actually a B-town construction.
So they've got a couple projects with them.
So I don't see.
I don't even go there.
I don't see that one from the river right now.
Nope.
That's a good thing.
Okay, remember their name, but not the same one.
I'll make a motion to approve.
Second.
Hi.
Thank you.
14 other new business of any, which is a resonance that's supposed to be this agenda.
Trustee Community announcements.
16.
This meeting will be continued from the council chambers and re-communied the staffers versus the purpose of executive session.